<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<contentList>
  <content contentuid="h85a0af48575e4483b2e4ddef5105e546" version="1">Amethyst Heartstone</content>
  <content contentuid="h71378090c52d48ffb54c0032373f7991" version="1">This large, captivating amethyst is more than just a beautiful gem; it's a conduit of potent arcane energy. Its deep violet hue shimmers with an internal luminescence, like a captured twilight sky.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2aed61d840e2405a814727aeea76e887" version="1">Staff of Channeled Power</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f2fb1a7e57e451280944a6694179e1e" version="1">This staff is a conduit of raw magical force. Crafted from a dark, dense material, its surface is polished to a high sheen, reflecting ambient light in distorted patterns.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf8a14eec13a74269b19d0d7b066e2459" version="1">Light Crossbow of Arcane Amplification</content>
  <content contentuid="h509888223bc848bd8404f206c994c3b0" version="1">Holding the crossbow, one feels a strange pull, a sense of connection to distant places, as if the weapon itself bridges the gap between yourself and the target, no matter how far.</content>
  <content contentuid="h09a31975227241af8ed209d1f4da5f81" version="1">Quarterstaff of the Twisted Weave</content>
  <content contentuid="hf134c812c38b452a8f1ebd009ffcdf0e" version="1">Woven throughout the staff are strands of a shimmering, almost crystalline material, which catch and reflect light in a subtle, mesmerizing way. These strands seem to pulse faintly, as if conducting a constant flow of unseen energy.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc188a34bed074ab4b6211fc722cee742" version="1">Light Crossbow of the Spellstorm</content>
  <content contentuid="h96bb0703f4ef48a9bac9488b5ce62b3d" version="1">The string of the crossbow appears to be woven from strands of moonlight, shimmering and almost translucent. A small, perfectly cut crystal of quartz is embedded near the crossbow's trigger mechanism, its facets catching and refracting light in a dazzling display.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5b3e69bdd2f4b38a60434e78e0b39b7" version="1">Staff of Arcane Resonance</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ed5d3a5f5564a1094e62cc4d7706658" version="1">Woven throughout the carvings are delicate strands of a silvery metal, which catch and reflect light in a subtle, mesmerizing way.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2ad2ecb83f27480280d38fb8d6237c11" version="1">Grimoire of the First Sorcerer</content>
  <content contentuid="hb06689af671048c981c1cf12977d8056" version="1">The front cover is dominated by a striking symbol: a compass rose etched in gold, its eight points radiating outwards from a central dark amethyst cabochon.</content>
  <content contentuid="had098192186b4abbbc7d37f0f812cf40" version="1">Sphere of Controlled Chaos</content>
  <content contentuid="h5383615e02f04c1f82141e3ced7d1a60" version="1">Holding the sphere, one feels a strange connection, a sense of immense power waiting to be commanded. This sphere, a creation of the Red Wizards of Thay, is a tool of immense and unpredictable magical force.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1d978e0714f54237944f47b61c8a0d81" version="1">Amulet of the Infinite Wellspring</content>
  <content contentuid="hbe2b8ec95f954f3eb4595ee29e79f4bc" version="1">This amulet is a masterpiece of arcane craftsmanship. At its center rests a flawless ruby, pulsating with a gentle, internal light. This gem is not merely beautiful; it is a conduit of raw magical energy, a miniature sun of sorcerous power.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3efb72df4fa4888aab714ba167b96ab" version="1">Band of Arcane Echoes</content>
  <content contentuid="h57aa9756abbf4b94b008807eb281f4e7" version="1">This band is crafted from a smooth, polished obsidian, its surface cool and reflective to the touch. Intricate, swirling patterns, reminiscent of echoes or reverberations, are etched into the obsidian, subtly shifting and rearranging themselves under close observation.</content>
  <content contentuid="h49ebac8279514ad79bcf2c95e1550d52" version="1">Ring of Sorcerous Supremacy</content>
  <content contentuid="hd49e5dfc11ae4c4da545c2408e4019e2" version="1">This ring is crafted from a heavy, dark metal, its surface etched with intricate, swirling patterns. The metal has a unique, almost matte finish, absorbing light rather than reflecting it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hccd5c22b7a2143caaa2345330303a6ab" version="1">Pouch of Sorcerous Sand</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f0f864c8c1a4fec9eef90f310af3458" version="1">The pouch is surprisingly lightweight and compact, easily fitting within a pocket or attached to a belt.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcf0a8a81c24b4f0893fb08990219816b" version="1">Ring of Subtle Sorcery</content>
  <content contentuid="h74305f119d1246f2b1b7b6c0a05acc27" version="1">At the forefront of the ring sits a single, perfectly faceted amethyst. The gemstone is not large or ostentatious, but its deep violet hue possesses an unusual clarity and brilliance, seeming to absorb and refract light in a captivating manner.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3664950010444ee8d3a9e84b58dc064" version="1">Metamagic Band</content>
  <content contentuid="h9267749c3d08426e9d34b579db1efe6c" version="1">This ring crafted from a blend of ancient bronze and shimmering silver, form a band that is both elegant and sturdy. The bronze portion of the ring is adorned with intricate runes and symbols, their meaning lost to time.</content>
  <content contentuid="h08a78aaa22bf40f9bdcfcce45e8cd4c7" version="1">Pendant of Arcane Augmentation</content>
  <content contentuid="hc0d620020312453da1ee1bef4908e415" version="1">This necklace consists of a smooth obsidian material, its surface a deep, reflective black. Intricate runes, glowing with a cool, cerulean blue, are etched across it, forming complex patterns. A single, vibrant blue sapphire, perfectly cut and faceted, is set in the center of the necklace, its light contrasting beautifully with the dark obsidian.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ca031bc85b14f628dea0f8a36af989f" version="1">Hood of Spell Mastery</content>
  <content contentuid="h1d4d6f66b468469e81d90206eaea1560" version="1">This hood is crafted from a fabric that seems to absorb and redistribute ambient magical energy. It feels strangely alive to the touch, pulsing with a subtle, internal rhythm.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5857bcb09d7747dcaf948557ef10f258" version="1">Robe of Ethereal Threads</content>
  <content contentuid="hd63249ac8a0a44f9b6afef2dde189f75" version="1">This robe appears to be woven from strands of captured twilight. It's a deep, shifting indigo, almost black in some folds, and shot through with threads of shimmering silver that seem to constantly rearrange themselves like constellations in a miniature night sky.</content>
  <content contentuid="h731ed8669a9f42afac9a9e0a6df32eff" version="1">Cape of the Fluctuating Ward</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a271405c9fb4650b7f28487c95a97a5" version="1">The cape feels cool and comforting to the touch, as though it radiates a gentle, soothing energy.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5773ce354bae458884603d8e979637f1" version="1">Shoes of the Spatial Swap</content>
  <content contentuid="hbc130fa6100d4de2b3d36ff832a7417d" version="1">Intricate, ever-changing geometric patterns are woven into their surface, hinting at pathways and distorted space.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5fe77e9f4f54399b102e83e29340874" version="1">Gloves of Sorcerous Might</content>
  <content contentuid="h0ee912bfbf1f40109553c00e688361c5" version="1">The gauntlets extend slightly up the forearms, culminating in elegantly tapered cuffs. Intricate patterns, resembling stylized lightning bolts or arcane glyphs, are tooled into the leather's surface.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9f9e5baa7cef440fbdbae4e8f7cb9900" version="1">Hat of Font Surge</content>
  <content contentuid="h983d473a0f2e4e8f8a6010954096969f" version="1">A series of thin, articulated plates of polished obsidian are meticulously sewn into the fabric, following the contours of the hat and providing a subtle, protective layer.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6cc0805a13984606a4b83fa8410e2d44" version="1">Robe of the Arcane Shroud</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2014b5fddc2496abc6b319af04b03db" version="1">Running a hand across the fabric evokes a sensation of static, a tingling promise of raw magical energy waiting to be tapped.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3051470744e540c9ab8587cc66ab1741" version="1">Cloak of the Sorcerous Soul</content>
  <content contentuid="hdf2c39d6cf564b29a74e8227385eb509" version="1">The cloak shimmers faintly with an almost imperceptible inner glow, as if imbued with a latent magical energy. The clasp that fastens the cloak at the neck is crafted from polished obsidian, its dark surface reflecting the crimson fabric in a mesmerizing display of contrasting hues.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f270320a72742a5a61c6d8bd8e8a09c" version="1">Boots of the Shifting Currents </content>
  <content contentuid="h009dd86a81b547a5997bd6a5f82d9d53" version="1">Lightweight and flexible, these boots feel as though they would allow for unparalleled freedom of movement. Small, circular inlays of polished moonstone are embedded at the heel and toe of each boot, their pale surfaces reflecting light like miniature moons.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f8825bdc35c48b08e2148fb9767ae92" version="1">Gloves of the Arcanist's Gambit</content>
  <content contentuid="h4598dd1e07684bb69093a57b516291a0" version="1">Intricate patterns, resembling interwoven strands of energy or constellations, are subtly embossed onto the gloves' surface.</content>
  <content contentuid="h44d9fc9ca10443439aa3b5670db7d86f" version="1">Hat of Rebounding Force</content>
  <content contentuid="h02daeb6ad0e846b09c94f2306a32bc4d" version="1">This hat is crafted from a supple, dark leather, meticulously stitched and shaped into a style reminiscent of a wide-brimmed adventurer's hat. The leather possesses a unique, almost oily sheen, and feels surprisingly light and comfortable to wear.</content>
  <content contentuid="h84064a4e5d5940f6b1a9c071e1192e4b" version="1">Robe of Shared Essence</content>
  <content contentuid="hb7bafe0c04804e53838533f87571b63b" version="1">Intricate patterns, resembling constellations or flowing rivers of light, are woven into the fabric, their designs subtly shifting and rearranging themselves with movement.</content>
  <content contentuid="hca41b3ae9bf04da99d3b2f7eee2f2ae1" version="1">Mantle of the Spell Current</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a8023fc0b3a4f1eba526824284df86d" version="1">The fabric drapes gracefully over the shoulders, possessing a surprising lightness that belies its intricate construction. The texture is subtly ribbed, giving it a unique tactile quality.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb190373e8c064c9a940e1b62ad9c4d5a" version="1">Boots of Arcane Haste</content>
  <content contentuid="haa0ed6998d1743a2bf2bee5e43fc8d55" version="1">These boots are crafted from supple, treated leather, meticulously stitched and reinforced at key stress points. The leather has a unique, almost porous texture, allowing it to breathe and conform perfectly to the wearer's feet.</content>
  <content contentuid="h54effb3d27e14a6a861a0ece8e860b91" version="1">Essence Weaver's Gloves</content>
  <content contentuid="h28e8cc496ec84ab09120d1d685730b9d" version="1">These gloves are crafted from woven strands of a silvery metal, each strand no thicker than a spider's silk. Intricate knotwork patterns adorn the surface, shifting and rearranging themselves in subtle ways as the wearer moves.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b001" version="1">Chaos and Control: Act 1 Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b002" version="1">Chaos and Control: Act 2 Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b003" version="1">Chaos and Control: Act 3 Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b004" version="1">Chaos and Control: Sorcerer Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b005" version="1">A backpack containing Chaos and Control Act 1 Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b006" version="1">A backpack containing Chaos and Control Act 2 Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b007" version="1">A backpack containing Chaos and Control Act 3 Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b008" version="1">A chest containing all Chaos and Control: Sorcerer Equipment</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b009" version="1">Charismatic Force</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b010" version="1">Once per turn, when dealing[1],[2], or[3] with spells, add half of your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Charisma"&gt;Charisma&lt;/LSTag&gt; modifier to the damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b011" version="1">Augmented Defense</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b012" version="1">While not wearing armour, you add your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b013" version="1">Sorcerer's Fortification</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b014" version="1">When you cast a spell and expend a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you gain +1 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;AC&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 2 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b015" version="1">Augmented Retaliation</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b016" version="1">If a creature hits you with a melee attack, they take [1]. (Once per turn).</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b017" version="1">Subtle Influence</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b018" version="1">You gain a +[1] bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellDifficultyClass"&gt;Spell Save DC&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b019" version="1">Arcane Acceleration</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b020" version="1">When you cast a spell of 1st-level or higher, your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; increases by [1] until the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b021" version="1">Living Current</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b022" version="1">When you cast a spell of 1st level or higher, you regain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to the level of the &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slot&lt;/LSTag&gt; used.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b023" version="1">Inner Tap</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b024" version="1">As a bonus action, you can activate the staff to gain &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt;. (Long Rest Cooldown).</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b025" version="1">Spellstorm</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b026" version="1">At the start of combat, the crossbow activates, causing bolts of magical energy to lash out. For 3 turns, whenever a creature attacks you, the attacker takes [1]. This can only occur once per turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b027" version="1">Magical energy lashes out at attackers, dealing [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b028" version="1">Arcane Symbiosis</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b029" version="1">When you cast a spell of 1st level or higher and expend a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to twice the spell's level + your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt;. These &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; last for 2 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b030" version="1">Kinetic Redirection</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b031" version="1">When hit by a melee attack the attacker must make a Strength &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; of 12, on Failed save, the attacker is pushed back [1] and knocked &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b032" version="1">Sorcerous Wager</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b033" version="1">Whenever you cast a spell and expend a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you gain a bonus to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Spell Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellDifficultyClass"&gt;Spell Save DC&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to the spell level cast. This bonus lasts 1 turn. (Once per turn).</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b034" version="1">Affected entity has a +[1] bonus to its spell &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and spell &lt;LSTag Tooltip="DifficultyClass"&gt;Difficulty Class&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b035" version="1">Sorcerous Sand</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b036" version="1">When your Metamagic ability is active, you may draw upon the enchanted sand within this pouch to fuel your magic, allowing you to cast 1 spell this turn without depleting your &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;. (Long Rest Cooldown.)</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b037" version="1">Costless Sorcery</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b038" version="1">Your &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt; total is not reduced when this ability is active.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b039" version="1">Sorcerous Restoration</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b040" version="1">When casting a spell and expend a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you have a 30% chance to restore 1 &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b041" version="1">Restored 1 &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b042" version="1">Sorcerous Potency</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b043" version="1">For every 2 unused &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; you possess, your spells of 3rd level or higher deal an additional +1 damage. This bonus damage can be applied up to a maximum of 20 &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;, for a maximum of +10 damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b044" version="1">Your spells of 3rd level or higher deal an additional +1 damage for every 2 unspent &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; you have.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b045" version="1">Echo Heal</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b046" version="1">When you cast a spell of 3rd level or higher and expend a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you regain a number of &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b047" version="1">Arcane Translocation</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b048" version="1">Arcane Translocation Used</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b049" version="1">After casting a spell, you can teleport up to [1] as a bonus action. (Once Per Combat).</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b050" version="1">You've used Arcane Translocation, you are unable to use it again until Long Resting.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b051" version="1">You can teleport up to [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b052" version="1">Point of Return</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b053" version="1">After expanding a &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you have a 15% chance to restore 1 &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Point&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b054" version="1">Twisting Weave</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b055" version="1">When you cast a spell of 3rd level or higher during combat, you gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on spell &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 3 turn. (Once per short rest.)</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b056" version="1">Your spell attacks have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b057" version="1">Arcane Extension</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b058" version="1">Increases the range of spells by 25%, this does not affect melee spells.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b059" version="1">Warding Magic</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b060" version="1">Arcane Shroud</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b061" version="1">A shimmering blue aura envelops you, swirling with ethereal petals. For the next 2 turns, elemental damage taken is also inflicted upon the attacker.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b062" version="1">Elemental damage taken is also redirected at the attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b063" version="1">Font Surge</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b064" version="1">As an action, you can instantly regain a number of &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to your Sorcerer Level. (Long Rest Cooldown).
</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b065" version="1">Might of the Arcane Font</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b066" version="1">Arcane Font</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b067" version="1">At the start of combat, your first spell that inflicts damage deals it maximum damage and deals bonus damage equal to your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b068" version="1">The first spell you cast that deals damage, deals additional damage equal to your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; and the damage dealt is maximized.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b069" version="1">The Endless Well</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b070" version="1">While your Metamagic ability is active, the amulet floods your being with raw magical energy, granting you access to its infinite reserves of &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b071" version="1">Chaotic Harmony</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b072" version="1">When you cast a spell, a random beneficial effect applies to the caster and allies within [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b073" version="1">Chaos Ball</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b074" version="1">You hurl a Chaosball from your fingers that explodes upon contact, torching everything in the vicinity dealing [1], [2], [3], [4], [5], [6], [7], [8].</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b075" version="1">A random beneficial effect has been applied.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b076" version="1">Reslient Soul</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b077" version="1">Add your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; to your Constitution &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b078" version="1">Echo of Forgotten Power</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b079" version="1">Forgotten Power</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b080" version="1">When you kill a creature, you have a chance to restore a random amount of &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;, up to a maximum of 5.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b081" version="1">Restore a random amount of &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b082" version="1">Spatial Swap</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b083" version="1">You can swap places with an ally within [1] of you.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b084" version="1">Flux Shield</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b085" version="1">While you have 2 or more unused &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you gain a +2 bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;AC&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b086" version="1">Your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; increases by +[1] while you have 2 or more &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="SorceryPoint"&gt;Sorcery Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b087" version="1">Heartstone Infusion</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b088" version="1">You have infused your weapon with the power of the heartstone, adding your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; instead of its Dexterity &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt;. (This effect last 10 turns).</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b089" version="1">Heartstone Parry</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b090" version="1">While the Heartstone is equipped, you gain a +[1] bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellDifficultyClass"&gt;Spell Save DC&lt;/LSTag&gt; and Armor Class.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b091" version="1">Maximized Output</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b092" version="1">When casting spells, you roll your damage dice twice and use the highest result.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b093" version="1">Phase Shift</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b094" version="1">Phase Shift Used</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b095" version="1">Once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;, when you take damage, you can use your reaction to take half the amount of damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b096" version="1">You've used Phase Shift. You cannot use it again until you take a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b097" version="1">Spell Mastery: Concentration</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b098" version="1">Spell Mastery: Infusion</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b099" version="1">Your spells have a chance to apply a random debuff. (Once per turn).</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b100" version="1">You're spells have a chance to apply, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLINDED"&gt;Blind&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SILENCED"&gt;Silence&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Fear&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SLOW"&gt;Slow&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="MADNESS"&gt;Madness&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b101" version="1">Chaotic Harmony: Ice Bloom</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b102" version="1">Chaotic Harmony: Mirror Image</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b103" version="1">Gain 3 &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="MIRROR_IMAGE_1"&gt;Mirror Images&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 3 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b104" version="1">Chaotic Harmony: Enlarge</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b105" version="1">You become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ENLARGE"&gt;Enlarged&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 3 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b106" version="1">Chaotic Harmony: Haste</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b107" version="1">Gain &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="HASTE"&gt;Haste&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 3 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b108" version="1">Chaotic Harmony: Elemental Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b109" version="1">Your weapon becomes infused with elemental power. It receives a +1 bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and deals an additional 1d4 damage of a random element for 3 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b110" version="1">Chaos Harmony: Action Surge</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b111" version="1">Chaos Harmony: Chaotic Heal</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b112" version="1">Chaos Harmony: Chaotic Heal</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b113" version="1">Chaotically healed for [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b114" version="1">Chaos Harmony: Shield</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b115" version="1">Chaos Harmony: Mystic Barrier</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b116" version="1">You gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on all &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt; and enemies have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on attacks against you for 2 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b117" version="1">Mystic Barrier</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b118" version="1">Chaos Harmony: Transformation</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b119" version="1">You transform into a random elemental Myrmidon for 2 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b120" version="1">Infuse your weapon with the power of the heartstone, adding your Charisma &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; instead of its Dexterity &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;Modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 10 turns.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b121" version="1">Only a Sorcerer can use this item.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27ad4a5fg8ebeg4b8egb71dg81a7d073b122" version="1">While &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Concentration"&gt;Concentrating&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you gain a +[1] bonus to Constitution &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
</contentList>