<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="c91a06c9-f1ae-49d1-ae5f-811b12a49101" version="1">Voidborne</content>
	<content contentuid="20cb0ab8-b687-4c34-9e66-ca3b8c5ee532" version="1">You are a failure of all magical arts, you have done nothing to improve your skills with a sword. But you kept trying even when time and time again you failed you never gave up. then one day a group of neighboring bandits decided to pillage your village, you fell at the first sign of struggle barely putting up a fight. In your last breaths gasping for air you herd a whisper... a voice of darkness from a distant place far from your own "i CaN GIvE yOu wHAt YoU SeEk" and instantly you gave in giving more and more of your self to this.. presence until there was nothing left yet it kept taking and taking past the point of anything left to take, it reviled all to you and you wish you hadn't taken its offer and yet you seem far more powerful then the rest but at what cost. you stand back up an insatiable hunger in your mind and heart...</content>
	<content contentuid="ccd7e0ad-ecd8-46a6-921a-89204b072b4b" version="1">Harnesser of the deepest shadows, the Phantom Strider wields darkness with unparalleled mastery. They drown themselves in obscurity, and fully give into to hungry nature allowing them unleash devastating necrotic power. The Phantom embraces the distortion of the darkness, casting demonic spells and enfeebling their adversaries.</content>
	<content contentuid="ca81df28-4378-43ee-935c-294c679e1d8a" version="1">Phantom Strider</content>
	<content contentuid="eb890cb4-93f2-467c-8d04-8718751098e8" version="1">Shattering beyond the boundary of dimension into light side of the Void through extreme thought of willpower in their dying moments. The Fate Spinner sat in a liminal space for what seemed like an eternity, flooded by all of the knowledge of multiple universes. Then one day they opened their eyes awake in a world they unsure is their own ready to fill it with their new found unlight.</content>
	<content contentuid="8eb1e274-e25c-4595-b659-23679a670339" version="1">Fate Spinner</content>
	<content contentuid="9de14ca5-c213-4325-bc4f-c6ff041e05ca" version="1">When a person is murdered in an extremely violent fashion they often end up in the shadowfell doomed to wander for eternity, when a soul truly resists this process making the very space and time warp around them. From the stress of a opposing forces dimension tears and the soul drops on the edge of the Void directly in the vortex that separates the light side of the void from the dark. Their body becomes filled with the energies both, slowly mastering the affects of time and space until they learn a way to return and make the world quake with the Void's influence.</content>
	<content contentuid="21c55852-69c8-49c1-8b0f-904400709274" version="1">Ethereal Weaver</content>
	<content contentuid="4c24d091-1805-47c5-bbf8-ce902da98e5a" version="1">Requiem</content>
	<content contentuid="a98b9ce6-515d-4a62-a48e-2ef206acacd4" version="1">The outer clans tell tale of a blade once held by an archangel said to have the ability to devour the soul of its target; its pulses with power, and glowed of unlight, its blade was lined with alien runes from a divine realm. Thus it became the requiem that all hear when drawn.</content>
	<content contentuid="22af2bbd-07b7-45ee-bc43-e531a6803fcd" version="1">Reforged in the Void</content>
	<content contentuid="a8ebb11e-edbf-4083-aa35-feab3ce66275" version="1">Requiem was left deep within the Void slowly absorbing its caustic unlight. Evil creatures also suffer extra physic damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="6bf29d5e-417a-4788-9734-62651df58cab" version="1">Requiem's True Master</content>
	<content contentuid="6315f4b2-4a1a-43f6-a063-2d1a238f517d" version="1">Requiem grows more powerful with its user, unlocks skills of those it has consumed in the past. The melee attack stat is always the highest stat of its wielder."It always sent a shutter down my spine when the old one drew his blade... Why? one asks... because i knew someone was about to die..."</content>
	<content contentuid="e54a83cd-cdde-4b23-b3f9-b262d099e0f6" version="1">Weapon Master Bonus Attack</content>
	<content contentuid="1a5c3c36-760c-4695-826f-30e3cd8387b5" version="1">When you land a critical hit or kill a target with a melee attack gain another attack.</content>
	<content contentuid="5d811911-bfea-43c3-a1f7-e7a2c03fa5ef" version="1">Undead Domination</content>
	<content contentuid="8e8c7005-1336-4b30-91f7-8ebcf1ce06bf" version="1">Using the souls trapped inside the sword force them to possess undead creatures in the area making them become your allies.(don't use on kethric breaks him)</content>
	<content contentuid="3cca6b26-435f-42b2-bd67-4c337eeb22e1" version="1">Herald's Command</content>
	<content contentuid="b9e9e586-8cbe-4320-bb66-8ab012a94896" version="1">Tear a rift open on your location for a moment dealing caustic unlight damage and making you ripple in space and time. Evil creatures recognize your sword and become terrified of you."deep in that darkness, long i stood there, wondering, fearing, doubting, dreaming dreams no mortal dared to dream ever before."</content>
	<content contentuid="c0525bc2-c415-435d-9c54-49a7fb9a2cae" version="1">Scatter</content>
	<content contentuid="9472ebcc-ae78-492c-941e-899c24b63c55" version="1">Requiem's blade separates into a thousand tiny, slender blade fragments, which fly away from the sword in a cloudlike formation.</content>
	<content contentuid="64b58a68-f50b-40f5-a210-138c600ec653" version="1">Ragebound Assault</content>
	<content contentuid="22d736a3-3cd5-412f-8875-aac1bc303b61" version="1">Take an aggressive stance before unleashing a flurry of 4 blows.(note this spell only works with an offhand and main hand equipped)</content>
	<content contentuid="d61131ad-52bd-42c5-b657-b925a16a9c11" version="1">Rave Dance</content>
	<content contentuid="a9f36a9a-972e-4a0f-8b4e-fdffa9c1c156" version="1">Slam your blade into the ground transferring many shards of Requiem along the ground before erupting them into weapons.</content>
	<content contentuid="10f548db-1ca7-4dde-b1a7-16b2cb778162" version="1">Summon Soul:Cobalt</content>
	<content contentuid="524a9a04-2ff2-419d-a8ed-380d052e1b73" version="1">Summon the soul of the legendary blacksmith from the clan Stormraven and wield one of her most cherished creations."Never again may i rest. Never again may i sit back in silence as one comes before, No they will stand in silence as i ravage their allies stricken with fear."</content>
	<content contentuid="f1f4a738-5c5a-4671-b99d-e9211b45211c" version="1">Cobalt</content>
	<content contentuid="4ed789af-1a3b-4ec2-be19-ff1300f07250" version="1">A sword made from the Legendary assassin clan Stormraven it is unknown how the soul of the blacksmith ended up in Requiem it was believed she died a peaceful life.</content>
	<content contentuid="712d956a-39ea-4aff-b839-08e4e870f15b" version="1">Impact Force</content>
	<content contentuid="f9c08c5d-a0ee-47eb-a376-f1a57d342294" version="1">Your strike has caused kinetic energy to build within the target causing a delayed explosion.</content>
	<content contentuid="0e18ca13-4ea3-4afa-a7ff-ab46bf47305e" version="1">Summon Soul:Cursebreaker</content>
	<content contentuid="46954df1-55d9-45b3-ab99-a3fdb47918b6" version="1">Using Requiem Summon the soul of the Curse Breaker within the blade and wield its power in the form of their signature weapon."To something as old and infinite as me the concept of one does'nt seem to make sense anymore." he exclaimed before cleaving the seemingly unbreakable curse on the boy in two.</content>
	<content contentuid="6a14b6cc-ce9f-49ab-96e9-2003e75fd04a" version="1">Cursebreaker</content>
	<content contentuid="2b25e2b1-1ff1-42b4-b9c4-0f5f0768685c" version="1">The blunt blade said to break any magical construction, despite its massive size it feels strangely light and a hum can be herd coming from it.</content>
	<content contentuid="d054a29b-f3a9-45ca-9666-57e42810e5d9" version="1">Summon Soul:MewMew</content>
	<content contentuid="126869d4-5ca2-4901-acaa-a20f0c7cf7b2" version="1">Using Requiem Summon the soul of MewMew in the form of an unbreakable hammer, infused with the power of a God of thunder."The old one was not known for his understanding and tolerance, he was well known for his cruelty and wrath." </content>
	<content contentuid="ee70338c-70f6-4b82-bcf4-b803c03b8066" version="1">MewMew</content>
	<content contentuid="h247f2738g4315g11eegbe56g0242ac120002" version="1">A legendary Hammer once thrown to quell another universe's world snake. the owner was felled by a redeemed God of War and the soul collected within Valhalla.</content>
	<content contentuid="8f3a21e6-5e16-4249-9316-50ccea85cb91" version="1">ImpulseCore</content>
	<content contentuid="4a40d795-a87d-4f09-a56e-dc26d20d00f5" version="1">Throw this legendary weapon causing a massive explosion.</content>
	<content contentuid="9fcdceea-3ede-4a7c-8cf4-e41d36fd0815" version="1">Summon Soul:Fayette</content>
	<content contentuid="2b3c4107-927a-46db-be9b-d3286c26be41" version="1">Call apon a long forgotten love to embrace you handing you the perfect weapon for desires of the heart."I've seen kingdoms across dimensions crumble, what hope do you think you have?"</content>
	<content contentuid="32a69622-220e-4f9d-b438-39941aff5464" version="1">Fayette</content>
	<content contentuid="2a5891ca-0f78-4102-9b06-3e6732fc2847" version="1">A dagger with gnarly serrations the thought of cutting yourself on them is oddly comforting.</content>
	<content contentuid="fa43d555-ea5a-4bbc-ad02-0ead40926bf2" version="1">Summon Soul:Scarlet</content>
	<content contentuid="9bd0dad7-7113-473b-b107-b4c09b96f9e2" version="1">Focus your fury into your blade and call upon a forgotten faithful ally."When they felt her raw power all shuttered and collapsed at my feet burned, Loosing all semblance of any strength left in their bodies."</content>
	<content contentuid="1b4decbb-061e-47b7-bbe7-04cf30d5e711" version="1">Scarlet</content>
	<content contentuid="3aa3ed86-e5c4-426c-ad7f-ed592db29d16" version="1">A glaive with a phoenix feather inlaid it once was used to quell an uprising in a legendary nation of voidborne. Its said that the more the blade is swung he hotter it becomes, much like its former owner it thrives off of an arrogant fighting style.</content>
	<content contentuid="33e050f3-48d0-463a-95a5-e41edba33407" version="1">Anytime fire damage is delt gain resistance to fire.</content>
	<content contentuid="n123456789444444444444444444444444444" version="1">Debug</content>
	<content contentuid="n123456789444444444444444444444444448" version="1">Debug [1]</content>
	<content contentuid="h656fba37gaf53g4bc4ga6dcg28f6b52c7791" version="1">Duskbound Mantle</content>
	<content contentuid="h251fe440g4ab6g491bgaf2ag60e949eee254" version="1">A robe that was left forgotten in the Void only to be found by the Voidborne.</content>
	<content contentuid="58539648-b043-4f40-9733-12615563505f" version="1">Unstable Essence</content>
	<content contentuid="453f90fa-060e-496e-89a3-fb26de635b11" version="1">Sonído:Unarmed</content>
	<content contentuid="b386ba10-f718-4e99-b911-25f7fdc44230" version="1">Teleport to an enemy and deal damage with your Fists and inflict additional radiant and necrotic damage upon impact</content>
	<content contentuid="7d10e12b-1bed-4eeb-a844-c05e1c9fbd4f" version="1">Sonído</content>
	<content contentuid="h0399244fg4fbdg4e14gac96g8b8dab186d4b" version="1">Teleport to an enemy and deal damage with your main melee weapon and inflict additional radiant and necrotic damage upon impact.</content>
	<content contentuid="89df9e11-0a77-4e1e-8d99-82d3568eb53e" version="1">Sonído:Shrouding</content>
	<content contentuid="f017c135-2bbe-4257-9e78-d2b61a4aca45" version="1">Mastering your manipulation of darkness, cause minor tears into reality after teleporting leaking unnatural darkness into the area.</content>
	<content contentuid="0e2b7499-8827-431e-8c16-c6cd68c54313" version="1">Dimensional Folding</content>
	<content contentuid="7d3eb278-6163-4daf-88ae-60a1c68251ec" version="1">Upon killing a target use the last moments of its lifeforce to slip into the dark side of the Void making you invisible as you flicker between dimensions. </content>
	<content contentuid="68433102-4128-42be-ae8b-6ad29db7b4b0" version="1">Shrouding Darkness</content>
	<content contentuid="d99b968c-8c29-498e-8fe1-35bb3e8bdede" version="1">Fade partially into the Void making harder to see you.</content>
	<content contentuid="72b78b3a-ead6-442c-a848-8007835db43a" version="1">Sonído:Slipstream</content>
	<content contentuid="6bf1877e-c545-46af-ac38-be080d241e41" version="1">your mastery over colliding forces allows you slip in and out of existence with ease giving you a unparalleled presence on the battlefield. Of course casting this way has unpredictable effects.</content>
	<content contentuid="242cbdf6-5bc9-4879-a6a4-d36e57d241bf" version="1">Sonido:Hypersonic</content>
	<content contentuid="52ad682c-6c3d-4a9f-b04e-9cb9fc88497d" version="1">Gather and convert mass amounts of darkness into unlight powering your body to the point that your speed becomes supersonic for a moment.</content>
	<content contentuid="6749eb2d-1622-406a-a33f-c7ab7bc23e16" version="1">Shade Flare</content>
	<content contentuid="660c9420-bb86-462d-b45b-24af3a0b920c" version="1">Conjure a ball of pure darkness then twist it into unlight before unleashing upon your opponent.Generates Loss Remnants</content>
	<content contentuid="1930214b-8b26-400d-a68e-7a8a6a6c714b" version="1">Unnatural Darkness</content>
	<content contentuid="be253d94-d14d-4612-8a3a-60e3072c504b" version="1">Tear open a very small hole in dimension allowing Unnatural darkness to pour through.</content>
	<content contentuid="c676f4d2-c00b-4064-a775-e1572d5a828c" version="1">Unnatural Darkness Mastered</content>
	<content contentuid="b32cc4cf-aa1c-463c-9f0d-248cbade5bb3" version="1">Rip open a larger hole allowing alot of darkness to come rushing through.</content>
	<content contentuid="57012619-093b-448d-a44b-b35a0a173938" version="1">Devouring Darkness</content>
	<content contentuid="a3d8721b-be4c-4179-a0db-74000a87b885" version="1">Gather natural light then begin to infect it with the aberrant darkness of the Void until it erupts into a stream of necrotic power.Generates Loss Remnants</content>
	<content contentuid="3abb4ace-6332-4895-858c-e1fb47a229c4" version="1">Loss Remnant</content>
	<content contentuid="342b8e02-b109-4229-90ec-e406396b0fbe" version="1">An imaginary substance left behind from your disgust with your opponent's weakness. Used to cast specific spells..</content>
	<content contentuid="6cd8cddb-fb5d-4452-93bd-479b513181c1" version="1">Loss Remnant:Stored</content>
	<content contentuid="8bf09b9f-cc69-429e-930d-405be7c66545" version="1">Your able to sense your own manifestation of disgust allowing you to channel it into a more advanced attack.</content>
	<content contentuid="804d8d99-dee7-4bfc-85a3-11b187dbd636" version="1">Mind Shatter</content>
	<content contentuid="db5ff476-c342-4520-8a99-16802ebc5c2b" version="1">Condense all of your hate, anger, and suffering in a single blast, steals your opponents willpower.</content>
	<content contentuid="e7e0c7ca-af65-48cb-80ca-6d43fa59657e" version="1">Thundering Radiance</content>
	<content contentuid="f8c5ec7d-74c4-4f52-9801-bb624ab14186" version="1">Wrap light over and over around the target until it begins to spiral devastating the area.Causes a minor rift in dimension sapping the target weakening them</content>
	<content contentuid="5e5c5a3c-c698-404f-8786-5b908b722729" version="1">Shredded</content>
	<content contentuid="24c96b10-f2e8-4d73-9c27-1565b1e1b755" version="1">This target has been devastated by the overwhelming power of twining light. has Disadvantage on attack rolls and all abilities.</content>
	<content contentuid="2d384c37-02dd-4970-bddc-50dd2130d0fc" version="1">Suppressing Gesture</content>
	<content contentuid="79086b84-01af-4e5f-b855-e43d79a301e8" version="1">Target suffers from 50% reduction in movement speed, disadvantage on attack rolls and all ability checks.</content>
	<content contentuid="329db054-e8b2-4ad0-8afa-83024cca4257" version="1">Temporal Rift</content>
	<content contentuid="d8938e2e-af7e-44aa-8e47-22ba830e5961" version="1">Focus a loss remnant onto a single point in space over shooting it. Causing a rip in space and time to the Void, Raining Chaotic energies down onto your target</content>
	<content contentuid="900ab8f6-2b9c-4326-9f9e-172d806d80d4" version="1">Refractive Sundering</content>
	<content contentuid="ad79d2f8-1776-4526-a984-c30459294625" version="1">You learn to lash dimension causing a distortion to occur when casting spells, adding force damage, based on your WisdomModifier+5.</content>
	<content contentuid="0cd13542-fe58-4f55-bf5b-b0ad0ab739d9" version="1">Eclipse Echo</content>
	<content contentuid="299f65d5-b9a3-4ef6-a180-bb857a8773ef" version="1">Teleport to 3 targets and strike them with lashing shadows draining their youth and weakening their attacks.</content>
	<content contentuid="23481be4-365e-401d-ae86-c00159cfe324" version="1">Wrathful Punishment</content>
	<content contentuid="42fb083f-9134-4636-8bfa-c5eaea5e462a" version="1">Surging with fury you grasp tightly onto all of the light in the area condensing it into a miniature nova before pointing it into a direction.Causes a massive explosion of light and cold damage</content>
	<content contentuid="0d6ae8f6-e866-439e-98ca-0af11cf97b43" version="1">Falling Despair</content>
	<content contentuid="4a5beb96-943f-42a3-9fde-baa3bdfbd16b" version="1">Giving into your paranoia has made you excessively prepare against your target, offering advantage on all saving throws,attack throws, and power you with necrotic power.</content>
	<content contentuid="570f0f05-9d15-42de-8aa0-338067da8bcb" version="1">Maddening Excitement</content>
	<content contentuid="6076a2f3-3503-4439-a5ff-561d21e eb788" version="1">Fighting such a difficult opponent has made you overjoyed into madness, your opponents shudder as they hear your sickening laughter form being stabbed by their weapons.Gain resistance to Slashing and Bludgeoning damage along with a shield.</content>
	<content contentuid="00b1fd46-8218-482f-b58b-5ca73ed4c740" version="1">Awakened Form</content>
	<content contentuid="h3cfc2250g4c7fg4db2ga8cag3f1c0907d1ab" version="1">Charge up a burst of power filling you and your allies with conflicting emotions to power your teams fighting style.</content>
	<content contentuid="c76eaef4-99d1-4827-a9b9-76d94f19dcf6" version="1">Devour</content>
	<content contentuid="69b1b421-d65c-432a-a54c-d88ef63a98b3" version="1">Combine one Loss Remnant with two Void Weave to form one Emptyness Plasma.</content>
	<content contentuid="b8708761-dd02-4c04-8d32-1dacbd08d399" version="1">Whispering Nothingness</content>
	<content contentuid="9164ac61-350a-4d32-89c3-534d4584d5a8" version="1">Strengthen your connection to the great indifference allowing you to constantly hear it whispering in your ear feeding you fractured knowledge granting a bonus on wisdom rolls.</content>
	<content contentuid="h39c24995g9252g4fd6gab56ge26290d7411e" version="1">Whenever you cast a spell on a creature, you can push or pull the target 2m away from you or towards you if the target is friendly, the spell hits it with an &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or it fails a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the spell.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc7d76bb3gc04bg4cf6gae12g6e7c4d1a6378" version="1">Whenever you cast a spell on a creature, you can push the target 2m away from you if the target is friendly, the spell hits it with an &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or it fails a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the spell.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2b7380bdgd6a0g4fa2gb2ccg768f2c629d5c" version="1">Whenever you cast a spell on a creature, you can pull the target 2m towards you if the target is friendly, the spell hits it with an &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt;, or if it fails a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the spell.</content>
	<content contentuid="6206527a-783b-4c8e-8bfc-2957c0f72669" version="1">When an ally within [1] of you hits with a weapon attack, you can use your Reaction to mentally connect with the ally. able to look through theith eyes summon many energy daggers to strike their target all at once and deal 1d10 Piercing damage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use this feature a number of times equal to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Wisdom"&gt;Wisdom&lt;/LSTag&gt; modifier, and you share these charges with &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_BindingSurgeFallDamage"&gt;Binding Surge: Fall Damage&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="4ce635f2-ed98-471d-a003-9a211f1eb7ad" version="1">Alter the effect of gravity on a target by increasing or decreasing the magnetism of the targets atoms for up to 1 minute or until your concentration ends.</content>
	<content contentuid="9255f27d-3e5e-4073-9a26-d0b7ced471cb" version="1">Infuse Void energy into a target causing a magnetism-like effect forcing them to seem heavier.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A creature's &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement Speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; is reduced by [1], and it has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="fa9c65ce-9265-4001-96ca-f5f314a6b1fc" version="1">Force a repelling effect on the targets atoms, greatly reducing its weight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A creature's &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement Speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; increases by [1], it can &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Projectile_Jump"&gt;Jump&lt;/LSTag&gt; twice as far as normal, and it has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Strength"&gt;Strength&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h930d1d88g2f03g47eag9f2agea26fbe5e36e" version="1">The Voidborne is emitting a powerful vortex of energy.</content>
	<content contentuid="79a8c688-ec46-4e49-a4c6-56c3652d3b2b" version="1">Whenever an affected creature starts its turn within the aura, it takes [1] on a failed save and its &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement Speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; is reduced to [2] until the start of its next turn. On a successful save, it takes half as much damage, and moving costs twice as much movement.</content>
	<content contentuid="67a89f53-8bc9-446d-a89a-2a18007f3209" version="1">The number of times you can use either &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_BindingSurgeAttack"&gt;Binding Surge: Attack&lt;/LSTag&gt;Replenishes on a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8e6567e2gfcdcg4effg9f50g90b4c9cffcc8" version="1">The number of times you can cast the Once Per Rest version of &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_EventHorizon_OncePerRest"&gt;Infinity Gate&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8cf8dbbega5c0g4900gb753ga3f670d2a916" version="1">The number of times you can use either Binding Surge: Attack You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier.</content>
	<content contentuid="b42eb875-a549-44e0-b51c-21604c0c65a2" version="1">Binding Surge Charge</content>
	<content contentuid="0700cbbe-6695-4a61-952a-6862d65dcf0b" version="1">Voidborne are disconnected from mystera and require relearning how to feel the weave. their spells are powered by the Void's corrupting touch taking the weave around them and making it "Voided"</content>
	<content contentuid="e53eea5e-0f48-4063-b4dd-cd370fc3c252" version="1">Void Weave</content>
	<content contentuid="8dcab626-ee1e-4675-917a-2d3543088351" version="1">A resource made from ones sheer feeling of emptiness and a desire of worth.</content>
	<content contentuid="22decdb3-4c9d-40b9-8eeb-bd26848d49db" version="1">Emptiness Plasma</content>
	<content contentuid="d4c54c46-0e4d-4c08-8e41-141b6d557845" version="1">Imaginary Essence</content>
	<content contentuid="fb6eb762-37ba-4630-a8bd-a2fb1316e549" version="1">The result of infinite Negative energy being forced into infinite Positive energy, forming a sense of nonexistence able to take the shape of any energy.</content>
	<content contentuid="4c7bda5f-79a0-4971-9059-7bc007292a2a" version="1">Infuse Energy </content>
	<content contentuid="e4f9cc8e-c457-469e-a4b1-9fedac5d3bbd" version="1">Charged Mass</content>
	<content contentuid="7d81745e-bcae-46f2-aa7c-2c83d347791d" version="1">Steal Substance</content>
	<content contentuid="cbe2448c-005e-49f0-bbe7-59b78a6869fd" version="1">Binding Surge: Attack</content>
	<content contentuid="692f65ca-0e4b-477f-a458-0448a1a25f37" version="1">Open a gate to your personal reality. Manifesting a power unique to you, causing targets in your vicinity to feel eternity. while caught in your infinity gate they are ripped appart by a vortex of power.deals force damage each turn and holds targets in place that fail a strength saving throw</content>
	<content contentuid="e3fa908d-fc10-417c-a384-213c054a7c35" version="1">Infinity Gate</content>
	<content contentuid="he025b65bg6586g49fegbcb1gb533ef05307e" version="1">Infinity Gate Aura</content>
	<content contentuid="1da4e701-6c85-4ade-81f3-6d6c7d2eac0c" version="1">Infinity Gate Damage Received</content>
	<content contentuid="268d90a5-d122-411f-af5b-013329ddd080" version="1">Infinity Gate: Movement Blocked</content>
	<content contentuid="4d8d6a73-e1b4-46b2-b0bd-0d01ac920cf6" version="1">Infinity Gate: Movement Limited</content>
	<content contentuid="hb0e01c1dg09d6g444eg9e83g5abc1e505d57" version="1">The target takes half damage, and moving costs twice as much movement for one round.</content>
	<content contentuid="h46c0417fg5071g4f90gbd69g2e4ac5946128" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; The object or creature must be Large or smaller.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha0ee8314gf6a5g4fc5g8b40g9f4894c8f4ea" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; The object or creature must be Huge or smaller.</content>
	<content contentuid="99b614d3-8f17-42f2-820e-977a40a7225d" version="1">Third eye</content>
	<content contentuid="c91057e7-c19e-40ca-a440-da90adf7a0c9" version="1">The Void whispers to you alerting to you or an ally to new threats granting a +[1] bonus to their Initiative &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt;. You are also the granted the ability to see in other forms of light ignoring darkness</content>
	<content contentuid="edd98f36-a3b5-4029-9990-313410de5296" version="1">+[1] added to Initiative &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt;. You are also the granted the ability to see in other forms of light ignoring darkness.</content>
	<content contentuid="149c9c3c-2b44-4202-9577-e5b0d9cc301c" version="1">Whispering Counsel</content>
	<content contentuid="7bed5858-734f-4400-ab9c-8b88199f24a8" version="1">Upon focusing you can hear voices in the darkness beckoning you, guiding you, to where? you do not know, only that they sometimes help with problems presented.</content>
	<content contentuid="36a26252-bd10-4830-9c4d-60efd378433a" version="1">You're listening to the voices you gain 1d10 to all ability checks.</content>
	<content contentuid="b46242b6-9fa6-4896-9a08-e3753a5bace6" version="1">Project Presence</content>
	<content contentuid="60733c1d-8d74-4597-8a9b-8991ee9243ff" version="1">Using your immense aura project power in a target area slowing anyone caught by the pressure.</content>
	<content contentuid="h18113c25g6b85g411fgac4eg5a7bf25e254e" version="1">&lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement Speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; halved.</content>
	<content contentuid="c0ea0694-d47a-4e56-abdb-6e4cb31b7a5f" version="1">Nebula</content>
	<content contentuid="6e3fb4f3-659a-44af-af7a-495cc91a48b6" version="1">Unleash intense pressure in a cone that possibly pushes or pulls creatures and objects up to [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="ha1cc2408ge0f4g42c9gb2e2g3024eab4d7f8" version="1">Targets still take half damage and aren't pulled or pushed.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2db4e095g717fg4674g80bege85837d32a1a" version="1">Deals an additional [1] and increases distance pulled or pushed by [2] per level.</content>
	<content contentuid="7a4cb8bb-0532-43b9-82cb-53718b5f8a90" version="1">Nebula: Push</content>
	<content contentuid="910ea851-acb8-4258-b516-9ff96fd456f6" version="1">Unleash intense pressure in a cone that possibly pushes creatures and objects up to [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="f0448c59-5e7f-4efb-a409-e5f2eeddde93" version="1">Nebula: Pull</content>
	<content contentuid="28129141-82f8-4500-af4c-cfd0f6b8d245" version="1">Unleash intense pressure in a cone that possibly pulls creatures and objects up to [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="36f81053-89fa-454f-b997-99b09a23be65" version="1">Voidformed Singularity</content>
	<content contentuid="h728f7a71g421bg42b2gbf2bg50ee199ee4c9" version="1">Targets still take half damage and aren't pulled.</content>
	<content contentuid="aff27d67-f895-4154-a9df-9c1882336c27" version="1">Convert emptiness plasma into an excessive amount of imaginary mass that pulls the very weave out of the air sending targets hurtling toward it.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb5107982g0597g4ff0g88a1g37187728dd0e" version="1">Vanished to another point in time.</content>
	<content contentuid="h67ac6db3gd3d3g4785g87eegb190bfa75e51" version="1">Targets still take half damage and aren't slowed.</content>
	<content contentuid="2a8ba4c0-5594-443e-a5bb-1b9564afdee2" version="1">Limitless Infinity</content>
	<content contentuid="0036e193-333a-4aba-ab12-a9f99e5d90e6" version="1">Pull the concept of infinity to the surface. creatures become slowed when trying to approach you, making it seemingly impossible to reach you.</content>
	<content contentuid="5913ccc2-2e41-4e15-8cff-cca2193ce56f" version="1">Limitless Infinity Active</content>
	<content contentuid="08e6fe6a-0481-471a-bcb7-02c700b7fe7a" version="1">you have a barrier active that will make creature have a hard time reaching you.causes disadvantage one melee and physical range weapons made against you.</content>
	<content contentuid="c24b9180-acb4-498e-b469-d60a474f9274" version="1">Weave Strum</content>
	<content contentuid="bb13b0fa-d8cb-4f13-b013-613b8f72094b" version="1">Grasp the weave within the air then pluck the thin lines of dimension connecting reality like sinew, causing a cascading explosive warping effect."Every living being is an engine geared to the Wheelwork of the universe. Though Seemingly affected by its immediate surrounding, the sphere of exturnal influance extends to an inifnite distance. come taste infinity with me."</content>
	<content contentuid="368fee96-d08c-45dc-89c3-d9f7d95fc0f4" version="1">Failed</content>
	<content contentuid="ef204855-b244-49bf-ab5f-495dd313fec3" version="1">Creature has encountered your barrier and have slowed down to a crawl</content>
	<content contentuid="e5e9fc85-bb72-48ff-a7e1-5657522acd5c" version="1">Saved</content>
	<content contentuid="06134bc0-3b26-4a66-a37e-2abca2160169" version="1">Targets movement speed has been slowed</content>
	<content contentuid="63b5e85c-24c6-4a88-9d4b-58e3ca0b3981" version="1">Voidcharged:Shifting.</content>
	<content contentuid="3944065d-c656-444d-bfe2-d47818b22a37" version="1">Focus and extreme feeling of Excitement and emptiness into your blade causing it to radiate power. Deals extra force damage, along with allowing you to use your wisdom stat for attacks and has jumping corroding Force damage on critical hits.</content>
	<content contentuid="624a5bd0-927f-4846-932f-1cd643e4e644" version="1">Voidcharged:Flooding.</content>
	<content contentuid="4ad61712-7f3d-41ef-b72c-62eaa5ea8be3" version="1">Forcing your rage onto your weapon causes a crack of energy that begins to spill out unlight increasing the kinetic power of the weapon.Causes Dazed, Crippled, Chest Trauma, on a crit. Voidcharged:Flooding also allows your attacks to use Wsidom as their primary stat.</content>
	<content contentuid="c2bb7121-aa1c-4591-b938-594e16b0880d" version="1">Voidcharged:Fading.</content>
	<content contentuid="eddde720-0813-44c1-97df-5e533b429f3b" version="1">Wrapping your blade in Devouring Darkness has caused it to flicker in and out of existence granting it the ability to pass through armor.Also allows you yo use wisdom as your attack stat.</content>
	<content contentuid="834e812a-cffa-4f2e-b238-1407aeeeefb7" version="1">Cleave.</content>
	<content contentuid="805c4bab-90f7-4d0f-9af9-17b1e47afdcd" version="1">Send a wave of emptiness toward your target causing them to bleed.Generates Loss Remnants</content>
	<content contentuid="c292acab-3ea8-4751-a29d-e0bb6918f8af" version="1">Dismantle.</content>
	<content contentuid="e3fb6196-d7c0-4662-bdb4-4cbebc9b3761" version="1">Using precision strike a target causing their defense to weaken.</content>
	<content contentuid="8797d2d2-f4cf-42e4-b7b7-3273b892c5cf" version="1">Maim.</content>
	<content contentuid="a9c82b08-6655-45f4-9a34-5213eca6a05b" version="1">Grasp a target and unleash a flurry of emptiness pulses.</content>
	<content contentuid="5f5c37f7-7a1b-4045-ad26-d4839df9b1a2" version="1">Dimension Slash.</content>
	<content contentuid="aaab7dd3-2a24-417f-be83-48219b03460c" version="1">Channel all of your suffering and loss into your blade then unleash it in a single sweep in front of you.</content>
	<content contentuid="1a0771ca-f045-4a0a-a288-7787bd349e30" version="1">Dimension Slash Cone.</content>
	<content contentuid="d1d2e749-60ac-4656-a50d-d78029542e03" version="1">Dimension Slash Burst.</content>
	<content contentuid="cd3d0b3e-aaa1-4b7f-ae01-fa80787aa75c" version="1">Dimension Slash Burst.</content>
	<content contentuid="b37b7aa1-f3e1-46be-bdbd-53ea0be02c9d" version="1">Channel all of your suffering and loss into your blade then unleash it in a single sweep around you.</content>
	<content contentuid="c5874433-70a8-4669-98e8-5a79f5e2e528" version="1">Malevolent Shrine</content>
	<content contentuid="a724fbe5-0236-4fd5-9385-d2bc3601a8d4" version="1">Open a gate into your Personal Domain that slashes at other creatures for up to 1 minute. For the duration, whenever an enemy starts its turn within your domain expansion they struggle to fight back taking a penalty to their attack.</content>
	<content contentuid="0f1ae90f-165f-4e52-907e-00ac3f5936db" version="1">Malevolent Shrine</content>
	<content contentuid="5a6ea6ee-7e2a-4ac2-81a0-f69d5bb18b4c" version="1">your gate is open and wrecking havoc on all</content>
	<content contentuid="e812d5bc-fbee-41ef-a196-7259f49322ad" version="1">Malevolent Shrine Damage Received</content>
	<content contentuid="e6e916b6-6dd3-4056-81f3-df9f13def3d7" version="1">Malevolent Shrine: Shredded, Attack Decreased</content>
	<content contentuid="65264f5f-83c5-4b96-85e6-d3dc32b7d05b" version="1">Malevolent Shrine: Dexterity Limited</content>
	<content contentuid="7f60264e-57e3-4f0a-b3c7-29650d45fe4e" version="1">Malevolent Shrined</content>
	<content contentuid="e2243e89-41ea-4d89-a751-34190abdec0d" version="1">Whenever an affected creature starts its turn within the aura, it takes [1] on a failed save and its Attack is reduced. On a successful save, it takes half as much damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="77513b55-b896-4eab-bbbe-fd0ce0cf8b0a" version="1">Gore</content>
	<content contentuid="5f159bdc-1b32-4bdb-b88d-28d11fbcf8a1" version="1">When &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;attacking&lt;/LSTag&gt;, every &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="GAPING_WOUND"&gt;Gaping wound&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLEEDING"&gt;Bleeding&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLINDED"&gt;Blinded&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CORRODED"&gt;Corroded&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DAZED"&gt;Dazed&lt;/LSTag&gt; status on your target will reduce the number you need to roll a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="CriticalHit"&gt;Critical Hit&lt;/LSTag&gt; by 1. This effect can stack.</content>
	<content contentuid="4c92b235-938c-4d11-9d0e-69df130003ce" version="1">Hungering Shadows</content>
	<content contentuid="27b83251-b6c7-48b8-a450-96622ca65b18" version="1">Things left in the dark begins to take damage from an unseen force."Don't you hear them?! The angels they call to me!" "Cresant dont be a fool, whispers in the dark are by no means angels."</content>
	<content contentuid="9304ebb5-18c3-4a69-b4ab-f962f62e128e" version="1">Something stalks this being damaging it at the start of each turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="5e4f0b00-4c7c-494a-875e-027ee1fb6f37" version="1">Damning Darkness</content>
	<content contentuid="59719a50-ca94-4b26-ac24-8de59f1b41ff" version="1">Stare into vile ancient darkness calling out to something very old and very malicious. Causes a large cloud of darkness not requiring concentration creatures within said darkness take Psychic damage each turn with a chance of cold damage."Come little children, come away with me, come to a fantasy filled with misery. I wont hurt you, not one bit, I'll let mother darkness see you're fit"</content>
	<content contentuid="134d310b-0165-4c7a-b83c-7dbf5b1f3d1f" version="1">This being is being oppressed by the darkness and will take Psychic damage each turn with a chance of cold damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="8f446d2b-17dd-4522-ac11-c9abf6e09cd5" version="1">Manifestation of Void</content>
	<content contentuid="01f48c4e-8b2f-4041-86a7-a0b85c2db923" version="1">Your very presence is corrupting and will tear open your target's wounds. If your target has &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="GAPING_WOUND"&gt;Gaping wound&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLEEDING"&gt;Bleeding&lt;/LSTag&gt; status,  your attack extra [1]. If has &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLINDED"&gt;Blinded&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CORRODED_1"&gt;Tainted&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DAZED"&gt;Dazed&lt;/LSTag&gt; status, deal further [1]. If has all five status, deal further [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="06440911-4ae4-4b12-a8df-fa8f5bee50bd" version="1">Light Purge</content>
	<content contentuid="37f8e672-55c0-49e9-a7c9-bc92c0372ec1" version="1">Generate a small amount of Void unlight to heal your self or burn undead</content>
	<content contentuid="f51cf8dc-9e31-4454-a36a-0081b65a28ca" version="1">Light Purge Far</content>
	<content contentuid="b8049702-43f8-4074-94c5-ce13b0371f62" version="1">Light Purge Mastered</content>
	<content contentuid="c0f3aa67-17dd-409a-a9c0-327b76155f9e" version="1">Burn Away Corruption</content>
	<content contentuid="d4504a85-a830-401d-abdc-e571f6b4c5d1" version="1">Use unlight to burn away vile poisons, disease, even restore sight, or mend paralysis. Causes 1D8 Fire damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="a580a8b4-2723-4b1a-83b0-71db3a3a4942" version="1">Essence Rip</content>
	<content contentuid="f7f53242-2825-463e-825d-91ea70441706" version="1">Using the Void's caustic nature. Form energy around the target then violently pull the power back to your own body to create a protective barrior around you</content>
	<content contentuid="d51df087-9980-49e9-a7c4-a82688cf64be" version="1">Covered in a barrier of pure energy</content>
	<content contentuid="160425ba-4eaa-4165-9780-e4f2e75b8011" version="1">Barrier Essence</content>
	<content contentuid="e912748a-5f0c-4d23-95b8-ade11cac5998" version="1">Tidal Surge</content>
	<content contentuid="0ef7fbcc-7594-4257-b2d6-64f9fff6194f" version="1">Sacrifice the barrier obtained from Essence Rip threading it into your allies Fates giving them a barrier</content>
	<content contentuid="9ce51fc6-48b3-444b-8d1c-f097585d12ae" version="1">Transisting Empowerment</content>
	<content contentuid="68f2e5f2-ae24-468b-a9f5-6e9fd1a0c561" version="1">Rip a hole in the Dimension to cause the Void's unlight to flood the area wherever you stand</content>
	<content contentuid="ef7be602-482c-4960-8d27-e7046acea25d" version="1">Transisting Empowerment Aura</content>
	<content contentuid="0a103fd3-0015-4e3b-b1da-dced72463b96" version="1">Unlight pours out of you</content>
	<content contentuid="683c7adc-250b-4d11-9713-615e72038e38" version="1">Healed</content>
	<content contentuid="20d2c2e2-861a-4efc-b68b-27568ce9a4be" version="1">You become healed from the mass amount of energy flowing through you</content>
	<content contentuid="b25125ca-788e-4399-a13d-f18a64c4301f" version="1">Damaged</content>
	<content contentuid="e86ef246-049c-4195-9a94-b278a96bf391" version="1">This target has begun to disintegrate from the power trying to break free</content>
	<content contentuid="25629979-cead-44f6-96b0-ef25be73aa6b" version="1">Enervate</content>
	<content contentuid="e45c4d61-4778-4cd2-aa43-6559733a0356" version="1">Touch the chest or your target causing a chain reaction of the essence within them burning into unlight.</content>
	<content contentuid="70147630-10cf-4758-bbbb-f5663e0a6e12" version="1">Enervated</content>
	<content contentuid="e762e954-3d80-463a-982b-e33a72c504a3" version="1">This creature is burning from the inside out so hot it burns creatures around them.</content>
	<content contentuid="e3f028f1-113e-4e33-8bed-a5910a875eb3" version="1">Burning</content>
	<content contentuid="51f5bb79-4382-494c-b1f5-92763b707380" version="1">This creature takes radiant and fire damage each turn for being to close to the enervated target.</content>
	<content contentuid="a6f3d4e1-2b81-4e6f-90da-8e4e3e175b21" version="1">Miracle Deluge</content>
	<content contentuid="bc7223e6-4c9e-4b1d-98bc-9e16582edfde" version="1">Take a deep breath and pause for a moment imagining serenity within your mind, you hear drops of water and feel a pitter patter on your shoulders before manifesting a miraculous deluge into reality.</content>
	<content contentuid="e5fc1099-aa6d-4d14-9f1b-5ee4534e0baa" version="1">Focused</content>
	<content contentuid="2b7e93e5-a8a0-4eef-bcd5-9b790d5ee011" version="1">Feeling the rain of serenity you now feel more focused then every before gaining advantage on attack rolls.</content>
	<content contentuid="1ddd4353-890b-4a54-a488-c7c37f7c7470" version="1">Invade Memories</content>
	<content contentuid="afd16eac-3820-4d3c-a457-5409d699e4cd" version="1">Burrow into multiple Creature's minds near by and plant false memories into their minds forcing them to hesitate from attacking you."I swear i just saw her over there...standing and starring....RIGHT THERE! Do you see her?! she is watching always watching...." </content>
	<content contentuid="e2bdbaf6-145c-4028-b0ec-20418f83083e" version="1">Corrupting Whispers</content>
	<content contentuid="61f3fb2d-496b-43f5-8df7-783f89bd5ea0" version="1">Call upon the great indifference to whisper sweet nothings into the targets mind slowly changing their perception of the world</content>
	<content contentuid="2bf205ca-2635-4c0d-8455-fc438864d2c2" version="1">Corrupted</content>
	<content contentuid="1e1dd04b-62d6-4091-8ac4-8703c021f68a" version="1">This creature has become corrupted and has succumb to the Void's influence until struck</content>
	<content contentuid="eac9df80-a8c2-45f6-9cd5-5dddd98d1077" version="1">Dark Vortex</content>
	<content contentuid="9a9a3c13-6747-4383-aef6-1daa69980554" version="1">Rip a hole in the sky an rain darkness down on all</content>
	<content contentuid="25e4bcaa-e65c-4ae9-9b70-d12a0993fd3d" version="1">Saved</content>
	<content contentuid="h428acfa3gc67fg4ab1g947fg713a140e1f2a" version="1">Light Vortex</content>
	<content contentuid="ed39e54b-f362-4de1-9df5-94b769a051cf" version="1">Command the sky with forbidden language open and rain Unlight on all</content>
	<content contentuid="19768d9f-d8bd-4319-9038-015288d139df" version="1">Chaos Vortex</content>
	<content contentuid="47b062ee-a9d2-471c-9bfa-c2bfb62344bd" version="1">Exhume such destructive emotions that the world begins to shake and a Chaos vortex appears in the sky</content>
	<content contentuid="b8ced298-5928-4298-a6fb-e65745d08e81" version="1">Tainted</content>
	<content contentuid="2a10114d-c452-4c40-bf9e-416726712012" version="1">This creature has the scent of Void-taint all over them each turn they are Tainted their condition will get more severe starting with an attack penalty.</content>
	<content contentuid="46f2800e-25bf-4452-9a2e-073199aed774" version="1">Scalded</content>
	<content contentuid="4860e68e-e716-4aab-b16b-0d1aa5e73996" version="1">Due to the spread of corruption this creature has severe burns making hard for them to concentrate.</content>
	<content contentuid="ae66e831-2e50-49f0-b6e4-f0a13669fa2b" version="1">Corroded</content>
	<content contentuid="0c170198-643b-414b-9cd9-60e748a7db9d" version="1">The corruption is deep within this creature burns drip from this creatures wounds eroding their armor.</content>
	<content contentuid="a4d49205-89a0-4bce-a17c-b3b900f2bd34" version="1">Eroded</content>
	<content contentuid="87f95ef6-6e5b-4fe1-b120-632b9b7fcbd9" version="1">The Void now shines through cracks on the creature, at any moment it feel like it could burst already lost to its madness.</content>
	<content contentuid="bbad4c93-946a-4b32-a6f6-6264c48be2dc" version="1">Blink</content>
	<content contentuid="01d2bd6f-db82-40d2-aa27-d606b3432837" version="1">Slip into the Void to end up somewhere else."No one knows what the word meant, but they sure did know what it did"</content>
	<content contentuid="d7be2fa4-8308-42b6-8f2d-2bb99800452b" version="1">Temporal Fissure</content>
	<content contentuid="e68ebf5f-6cbb-474f-81ec-28a91648c36c" version="1">You have mastered the art of weaving void energy into elemental affording you the power to cause dimensional strain resulting in a pulse of semi shaped energy.Generates Loss Remnants</content>
	<content contentuid="601f3b23-facd-4d2b-824c-64f621b50253" version="1">Flash of Unlight</content>
	<content contentuid="dd1fdc02-3394-473d-b310-d774f11e7d15" version="1">Condense a small flash of Void Unlight into your hand then let it escape through the shape of a triangular hand sign stuning,blinding and corroding the target.</content>
	<content contentuid="7a921718-c0de-44a4-8440-ffb63c60339d" version="1">Cascading Strike</content>
	<content contentuid="f5b49b81-89fe-4773-81ec-bcf057669e3d" version="1">Focus raw emptiness into a crystalline state then project into a blade at your opponent causing it to erupted into spikes across their body.</content>
		<content contentuid="482c1544-ec60-48a1-a1e1-2dcc19601884" version="1">Divine Flame</content>
		<content contentuid="1bce91b6-f879-46d0-841d-3b282c04d795" version="1">"Furnace Open,Kamino"</content>
	<content contentuid="8d2b046c-6765-4417-9d49-4bb4c6b98962" version="1">Jogo's Demise</content>
	<content contentuid="c435bd57-db8f-49cb-8f9f-163a7b571ddd" version="1">Stand proud, you're strong</content>
	<content contentuid="2701be53-ee4e-4b70-99f5-5acc68650269" version="1">Pumkin The Hamdini</content>
	<content contentuid="8fad23d2-18f4-492a-abd5-7f880038e1ec" version="1">Summon:Pumpkin The Hamdini</content>
	<content contentuid="eea1ca2d-fc20-4fb9-bac6-97349c2b7087" version="1">Summon the elusive Hamdini master of escaping all manner of prisons</content>
	<content contentuid="a8e58f1e-64cd-4a53-9fb2-90c13b1bf57d" version="1">Gizmo The Destroyer</content>
	<content contentuid="fad54a25-49b3-4472-b25e-60e2868ba97b" version="1">Summon:Gizmo The Destroyer</content>
	<content contentuid="14379344-6c41-4e2f-870f-40f341f55720" version="1">Corrosive Bite</content>
	<content contentuid="ad1c256a-3e26-4ae3-be0a-1171147a1242" version="1">Clamp onto your target spreading your unatural corruption.</content>
	<content contentuid="b3d17b30-8eb8-45e8-b19c-2c73501dde21" version="1">Summon the mighty Hammuri from an alternate dimension ready to destroy all in his path. "my sword is sharp and my hamster hungry".</content>
	<content contentuid="50aec4a7-ccc7-4e32-b8d0-43ad0622ade3" version="1">The Space Hamster has mastered the technique maximizing its healing effect.</content>
	<content contentuid="4d9718f9-a537-48c8-be40-49e157660771" version="1">Due to the Flickering existence of A Space Hamster They are able to alter the Fate of others</content>
	<content contentuid="02947ffd-5e78-41bf-ad57-be201eb045eb" version="1">The giant space hamster struggles with this spell, but pulls if off none the less</content>
	<content contentuid="cc81568c-9048-470d-93fa-ee0b142a2e6c" version="1">VoidShard</content>
	<content contentuid="b51628c2-0de1-4a2d-8e98-3e9999529665" version="1">Pull a sword of imaginary substance from your chest that acts like a ghost blade.(only works in honour mode currently)</content>
	<content contentuid="f5a2d2b4-8dbc-4e77-b289-977d17fa1e96" version="1">Spectre Slash</content>
	<content contentuid="d511fcce-bc72-4ff2-b25d-6d3d9b87a56b" version="1">The Voidshard's blade passes through the target causing significant mental strain.</content>
	<content contentuid="8b096ac1-6392-47f8-9437-7df83df8028d" version="1">Gerbs!</content>
	<content contentuid="88172be0-5ce2-4f35-96ae-7963f3fc1c64" version="1">Summon three Astral Gerbils, one that infects,one that corrodes, and one that bleeds their targets.</content>
	<content contentuid="1497eafe-fc31-4c18-a07a-bbff3547e374" version="1">Tony</content>
	<content contentuid="49e08ffe-d4a7-4f89-9505-2ddf1d774a08" version="1">Owen</content>
	<content contentuid="353bec42-ad6d-452d-b4c4-4e267edf1955" version="1">Nibs</content>
</contentList>